adbrook.com 2015-05-10

# AdBrook

What information do we collect? 

  * We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order or fill out a form. 
  * When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for? 

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

  * To personalize your experience

(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

  * To improve customer service

(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)

Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

How do we protect your information? 

  * We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. 
  * We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.
  * Transactions are only completed through processor accounts where the only information stored is your username, email, or ezy id (depending on the processor used).

Do we use cookies? 

  * Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
  *  We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties? 

  * We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  * Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. Members and advertisers also display third party content and links as included with purchased services on our website.  These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

  * Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
  * As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our AdBrook site may edit their personal information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the 'Edit Profile' page.

Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance 

  * We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 18 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 18 years old or older.

Terms and Conditions 

  * Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website at 

Your Consent 

  * By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy 

  * If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

This policy was last modified on June 19, 2013

Contacting Us 

  * If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

To official Adbrook's start left: d, h, min, s
